Guide to the David Plowden Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1948-2011; Series I; 189; 41.9 linear_feet
  - July 1995 Acquisition
    - Reproducible Prints and Study Prints
      - Detail, Scroll Work on Newburgh-Beacon Ferryboat Orange (NBF-163-111) Reproducible print, 1963 January (Box 102)
      - Ellis Island Ferry, Ferryboat Ellis Island (abandoned). Ellis Island, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1962 May (Box 102)
      - Ferry and Passenger Terminal, New York Central Railroad, West Shore, Destroyed by Fire, 1961. Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - Ferry Bienville, one of 2 Summer Boats, Arriving at Lévis, Quebec, on La Traverse de Lévis. Cité de Lévis, Quebec, Canada (864-210 or 864-40) Reproducible print, 1964 August (Box 102)
      - Ferry Brinkerhoff, Abandoned on Pawcatuck River. Pawcatuck, Connecticut (CT-1263-6) Reproducible print, 1963 December (Box 102)
      - Ferry Brinkerhoff, Abandoned on Pawcatuck River. Pawcatuck, Connecticut (CT-1263-81) Reproducible print, 1963 December (Box 102)
      - Ferry Brinkerhoff, Abandoned on Pawcatuck River. Pawcatuck, Connecticut (CT-1263-89) Reproducible print, 1963 December (Box 102)
      - Ferry Collector (Ticket Collector), Central Railroad of New Jersey, Liberty Street Ferry, Liberty Street Ferry house. New York, New York (CNJ-467-492) Reproducible print, 1967 April (Box 102)
      - Ferry Ellis Island, Abandoned at Ellis Island. Ellis Island, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1962 May (Box 102)
      - Ferryboat Bienville (one of 2 Summer Boats), La Traverse de Lévis (Levis Ferry), St. Lawrence River. Cité de Lévis, Quebec, Canada (864-209) Reproducible print, 1964 August (Box 102)
      - Ferryboat Binghamton, Pilothouse, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-1053) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Ferryboat Ellis Island, Abandoned at Ellis Island. Ellis Island, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1962 May (Box 102)
      - Ferryboat Ellis Island. Ellis Island, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1962 May (Box 102)
      - Ferryboat Interior, Newburgh-Beacon Ferry. Beacon, New York (NBF-863-31) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Ferryboat Wake, Newburgh-Beacon Ferry. Hudson River, New York (NBF-363-21) Reproducible print, 1963 March (Box 102)
      - Ferryhouse. Beacon, New York (NBF-863-27) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Former New York Central Railroad Ferryboat Niagara, used as Office for New Jersey Public Service Corps. Carteret, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - Fruit Stand, New York Central Railroad Passenger and Ferry Terminal, Destroyed by Fire, 1961. Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959? (Box 102)
      - Gate, Ferryboat Elmira, Hoboken Ferry, Last Day of Operation, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-556) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - George Schomp, Deck Hand, Ferryboat Elmira, Hoboken Ferry, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad, Last Day of Operation (EL-1167-235) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Guemes Island Ferry. Washington (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1962 July (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry (Last Day), Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-992) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Commuters on Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-35-38) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Commuters on Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-35) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Ferryboat Binghamton, Arrival at Barclay Street. New York, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1960? (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Ferryboat Binghamton, Arriving at Barclay Street Ferry Terminal. New York, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1960? (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Ferryboat Chatham, Arriving at Hoboken Ferry Terminal. Hoboken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Ferryboat Chatham, Commuters at Hoboken. Hoboken, New Jersey (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Ferryboat Maplewood at Barclay Street. New York, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1960? (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Ferryboat Maplewood, Lackawanna Railroad (FB/DL) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, interior [of] Ferryboat Scranton, built 1904. Hoboken, New Jersey (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1967 (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Lackawanna Railroad, Barclay Street. New York, New York (FB/DL) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Lackawanna Railroad, Barclay Street. New York, New York (FB/DL) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry, Last Day, Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-560) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Hoboken Ferry Saloon on Ferryboat Scranton (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Hudson River Day Liners, Alexander Hamilton on the left, and Peter Stuyvesant on the right, in Winter Lay-Up (ST-NYC-263-160) Reproducible print, 1963 February (Box 102)
      - Jim Brown, Stoker/Fireman, Ferryboat Elmira (EL-1167-188) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad (West Shore) Ferry and Passenger Train Terminal (destroyed by fire, 1961). Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad (West Shore) Ferry House and Railroad Passenger Terminal. Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad (West Shore), Passenger and Ferry Terminal (destroyed by fire, 1961). Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad (West Shore), Passenger and Ferry Terminal. Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad (West Shore), Passenger Train and Ferry Terminal (destroyed by fire, 1961). Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad Passenger Terminal and Ferry Terminal. Weehawken, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tug #3 (No number extant) Study print, undated (Box 102)
      - New York Central Railroad Steam Tugs, Last Fleet of Steam Tugs in U. S., Built Between 1900-1923. New York City Harbor, New York (NYH-ST-NYC-363-83) Reproducible print, 1963 March (Box 102)
      - Newburgh Ferry. Newburgh, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Newburgh Ferry, Ferryboat Orange, Arriving in Newburgh. Newburgh, New York (Probably NBF-1163-7) Reproducible print, 1963 (Box 102)
      - Newburgh Ferry, Interim Waiting Room, Beacon Ferryhouse (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Newburgh Ferryhouse, Detail, Delaware, Lackawanna Western Railroad (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1963 January (Box 102)
      - Newburgh, New York (NBF-1163-616) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry. Newburgh, New York (NBF-1163-395) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry. Hudson River, New York (NBF-163-76) Reproducible print, 1963 January (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Orange. Newburgh, New York (NBF-863-54) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Orange, Captain Salmon, Last Day (NBF-1163-375) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Orange, Crossing Hudson, Looking South from Ferryboat Dutchess (NBF-863-34) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Orange, Gate. Newburgh, New York (NBF-1163-721) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Orange, Laid Up at Beacon (NBF-863-1) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Orange, Laid Up at Beacon. Beacon, New York (NBF-863) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Orange, Wheelhouse. Newburgh, New York (NBF-1163-43) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry Racks, Beacon Ferry Slip (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Beacon Ferryhouse. Beacon, New York (NBF-863-2) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Beacon Ferryhouse. Beacon, New York (NBF-163-136) Reproducible print, 1963 January (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Captain Atkins, Ferryboat Orange (NBF-1163-612) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Doorway on Upper Slip, Beacon Ferryhouse (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Ferryboat Orange, Seen through Newburgh Ferryhouse Window (NBF-863-89) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, John Miller, Engineer, Ferryboat Orange. Hudson River, New York (NBF-1163-853) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Newburgh Ferry Ship looking across Hudson at East Hudson River, New York (NBF-863-57) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Newburgh Ferryhouse (NBF-1163-133) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferry, Rack Detail, Beacon Ferryhouse (NBF-1163-548) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Ferryboat Orange, Firing Boilers, Last Day (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Passenger on Ferryboat Pocono, Hoboken Ferry, Lackawanna Railroad (FB/DL) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 102)
      - Passenger on Ferryboat Scranton, Hoboken Ferry, Lackawanna Railroad (FB/DL) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 102)
      - Passengers on Ferryboat Pocono, Hoboken Ferry, Lackawanna Railroad (FB/DL) Reproducible print, 1960 (Box 102)
      - Petersen's Lighterage Co., Steam Lighter Victor. New York City Harbor, New York (NYH-TD-314) Reproducible (plus) print, undated (Box 102)
      - Pilot House, Ferryboat Ellis Island, Abandoned at Ellis Island. Ellis Island, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1962 May (Box 102)
      - Pilot House, New York Central Railroad #10, Steam Tug. Weehawken, New Jersey (NYH-ST-NYC-263-29) Reproducible (plus) print, 1963 February (Box 102)
      - Pilot House, New York City Railroad Steam Tug #32. New York City Harbor, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Pilot House, Newburgh Ferryboat Orange (NBF-1163-263) Reproducible print, 1963 November (Box 102)
      - Pilot Wheel Detail, Ferryboat Binghamton, Hoboken Ferry, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad. Hoboken, New Jersey (EL-1167-1053) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Railroad of Central New Jersey. Ferries Elizabeth and Red Bank, at Jersey City Ferry Terminal. Jersey City, New Jersey (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Seo Schomp, Deckhand, Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad, last day (EL-1167-233) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - SS Nobska, Arriving at Woods Hole. Woods Hole, Massachusetts (865-324) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 102)
      - SS Nobska, Arriving at Woods Hole. Woods Hole, Massachusetts (865-326) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 102)
      - SS Nobska, Departing Woods Hole. Woods Hole, Massachusetts (865-383) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 102)
      - SS Nobska, off Oak Bluff. Martha's Vineyard, Massachusetts (865-297) Reproducible print, 1965 August (Box 102)
      - Stack, New York Central Railroad Steam Tug #32 (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - Staten Island Ferry, Ferryboat Docker (NYH-2-23-13-10) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Steamer Alexander Hamilton (HR/DL-863-155) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Steamer Alexander Hamilton Leaving Bear Mountain Landing, Hudson River Day Line. Hudson River, New York (HP/DL-863-85) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Steamer Alexander Hamilton, Hudson River Day Line (HR/DL-863) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill Former Hudson River Freight Boat, Operating as Ferry Between Port Jefferson, New York and Bridgeport, Connecticut (665-234) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Bridgeport, Connecticut to Port Jefferson, New York Ferry, Arriving at Port Jefferson. Port Jefferson, New York (665-90) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Former Hudson River Freight Boat (last extant example), Operating as Ferry between Port Jefferson, New York and Bridgeport, Connecticut (665-234) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Former Hudson River Freight Boat, on Cross Long Island Sound, between Bridgeport, Connecticut and Port Jefferson, New York (665-158) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Former Hudson River Freight Boat, on Cross Long Island Sound, between Bridgeport, Connecticut and Port Jefferson, New York (665-163) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Former Hudson River Freight Boat, on Cross Long Island Sound, between Bridgeport, Connecticut and Port Jefferson, New York (665-143) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Former Hudson River Freight Boat, on Cross Long Island Sound, between Bridgeport, Connecticut and Port Jefferson, New York (665-166) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Former Hudson River Freight Boat, on Cross Long Island Sound, between Bridgeport, Connecticut and Port Jefferson, New York (665-159) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer Catskill, Former Hudson River Freight Boat, on Cross Long Island Sound, between Bridgeport, Connecticut and Port Jefferson, New York (665-142) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg (NYH-963-14) Reproducible print, 1963 September (Box 102)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg at Bear Mountain Landing, New York, Hudson River. Bear Mountain Landing, New York (665-221) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg leaving Bear Mountain Landing. Bear Mountain Landing, New York (665-223) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg, Arriving at Battery Park. Battery Park, New York (963-12) Reproducible print, 1963 September (Box 102)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg, Arriving at the Battery, Captain Bunce in Command. Battery Park, New York (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1963 September (Box 102)
      - Steamer City of Keansburg, Under Bear Mountain Bridge. Bear Mountain Landing, New York (665-220) Reproducible print, 1965 June (Box 102)
      - Susquehanna River Ferries Roaring Bull on the left and Falcon in the foreground (FBA-S-962-4) Reproducible print, 1962 September (Box 102)
      - Tugboat Captain, New York Central Railroad Steam Tug. New York City Harbor, New York (NYC-ST-363-46) Reproducible print, 1963 March (Box 102)
      - Twenty-four Mile Ferry. On Columbia River, near Revelstoke, British Columbia, Canada (GFB-68-5166) Reproducible print, 1968 (Box 102)
      - "Van", Dropping Rudder Pin to Keep Rudder Locked in Place While Operating in Opposite Direction, Ferryboat Elmira, Hoboken Ferry, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-245) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik (foreground) and Jim Brown, Firemen/Stokers, Ferryboat Elmira (EL-1167-189) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik (foreground) and Jim Brown, Stokers/Firemen, Ferryboat Elmira (EL-1167-191) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik in the foreground, Jim Brown in the background, Firemen/Stokers on the Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-193) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik, Stoker, Ferryboat Elmira, Hoboken Ferry, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-197) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik, Stoker, Ferryboat Elmira, Pulling Fires, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-196) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik, Stoker, Pulling Fires, Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-35) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik, Stoker, Pulling Fires, Ferryboat Elmira, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-35) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Walter Kowalik, Stoker, Pulling Fires, Ferryboat Elmira, Hoboken Ferry, Erie-Lackawanna Railroad (EL-1167-199) Reproducible print, 1967 November (Box 102)
      - Wheelhouse (Pilot House), Ferryboat Pocono, Erie Lackawanna Railroad, Built 1905 (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 102)
      - [Hoist on Tug Boat] (No number extant) Reproducible print, undated (Box 103)
      - [Steamer Victor] (No number extant) Reproducible (plus) print, undated (Box 103)
      - A-Deck Stairwell, Steamer Richelieu, Canada Steamship Lines (834-339) Reproducible print, 1964 August (Box 103)
      - Abandoned Ferries Used as Homes. Sausilito, California (FBA-SFO-762-51) Reproducible print, 1962 July (Box 103)
      - Abandoned Ferry Ship, McArthur Kill. Staten Island, New York (No number extant) Study print, 1959 (Box 103)
      - Alexander Hamilton Leaving Bear Mountain Landing, New York, Hudson River. Bear Mountain Landing, New York (HR/DL-863-22) Reproducible print, 1963 August (Box 103)
      - Algoma Central and Hudson Bay Railroad, Freighter Algosoo, built 1901, Showing Counter Stern. Midland, Ontario, Canada (964-583) Reproducible print, 1964 September (Box 103)
      - Ann Arbor Railroad, Ann Arbor Number 5, Car Ferry Arrives Manitowoc, Wisconsin from Frankfort, Michigan. Great Lakes, Michigan (964-511) Reproducible print, 1964 September (Box 103)
      - Ann Arbor Railroad, Ann Arbor Number 5, Lake Michigan Car Ferry. Menominee, Michigan (964-463) Reproducible print, 1964 September (Box 103)
      - Arkansas II, Steam Snag Boat, United States Army Corps of Engineers, Mississippi River. Memphis, Tennessee (1064-807) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 103)
      - Baton Rouge Ferry, City of Baton Rouge (left) and Louisiana (right), Mississippi River. Baton Rouge, Louisiana (1064-178) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 103)
      - Baton Rouge Ferry, City of Baton Rouge (right) and Louisiana (left); Mississippi River. Baton Rouge, Louisiana (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 103)
      - Baton Rouge Ferry, Ferry Boat Louisiana, Mississippi River. Baton Rouge, Louisiana (No number extant) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 103)
      - Baton Rouge Ferry, Mississippi River (1064-209) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 103)
      - Bay Ridge Water and Lighterage Water Boat Aqua, New York Harbor. New York, New York (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1963 (Box 103)
      - Belle of Louisville (1064-469) Reproducible print, 1964 October (Box 103)
      - Bow fender, New York Central Railroad Steam Tug. Weehawken, New Jersey (No Number Extant) Reproducible print, 1959 (Box 103)
      - Bow View, SS Richelieu, Canada Steamship Line (864-481) Reproducible print, 1964 August (Box 103)
      - Brooklyn Eastern Railroad District Terminal Steam Tug, Replacing Fenders. New York, New York (No number extant) Study print, 1961 (Box 103)
      - Builders Plate, SS Keewatin, Canadian Pacific Railway. Port McNicoll, Ontario, Canada (964-559) Reproducible print, 1964 September (Box 103)
      - Bush Terminal Company Tug Irving T. Bush, Delivering Car Floats to Lehigh Valley Railroad Float Bridges. Jersey City, New Jersey (No number extant) Study print, 1962 February (Box 103)
      - Bush Terminal Railroad Company Sole Tug, the Irving T. Bush, Delivers Car Float Number 45 to the Lehigh Valley Railroad's Jersey City Float Bridges. Jersey City, New Jersey (RR-NY - Marine operations) Study print, 1962 February (Box 103)
      - Bush Terminal Railroad Company Sole Tug, the Irving T. Bush, Delivers Car Float Number 45 to the Lehigh Valley's Float Bridges at Jersey City, Adjacent to the CNJ Ferry Terminal and Pan Station. Jersey City, New Jersey (RR-NY - Marine operations) Study print, 1962 February (Box 103)
      - C O Railroad Lake Michigan Car Ferry, Spartan (left, built 1952, probably last coal freight passenger carrying vessel built in United States) and Diamond Alkali (right, still unloading steam decker). Ludington, Michigan (963-20) Reproducible print, 1963 September (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railway Steamer Lansdowne on Detroit River approaching Detroit, Michigan (464-125) Reproducible print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railway Steamship Lansdowne, built 1884, crossing Detroit River toward Windsor, Ontario. Detroit River (464-1055) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railways, Detroit River Car Ferry Huron, built 1875. Detroit River (CF-DR-963-89) Reproducible print, 1963 September (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railways, Detroit River Car Ferry Lansdowne Side Wheeler, built in 1884. Detroit River (464-846) Reproducible print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railways, Detroit River Car Ferry Lansdowne, Side Wheeler, built in 1884 (464-95) Reproducible print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railways, Lansdowne, Detroit River Car Ferry, built 1884 (464-873) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railways, Railroad Car Ferry Lansdowne, built 1884. Detroit River (464-1020) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railways, Steamer Lansdowne Showing Port Side Paddle Box, built 1884, Detroit River Railroad Car Ferry, Canadian National Railways (464-8) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian National Railways, Steamer Lansdowne, Paddle Wheel, built 1884, Detroit River Car Ferry, Railroad Car Ferry, Canadian National Railway (464-370) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Canadian Pacific Railway, Great Lakes Steamship Service, SS Keewatin, Bridge and Bow (964-600) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 September (Box 103)
      - Captain Marshall, Ferry Boat Albany, New York Central Railroad, Weehawken Ferry (No Number Extant) Study print, undated (Box 103)
      - Car Ferry Chief Wawatam at Mackinaw City, Michigan, Railroad Car Ferry across Straits of Mackinac (MI-963-29) Reproducible print, 1963 September (Box 103)
      - Car Ferry Lansdowne, built 1884, Canadian National Railways, Detroit River (464-96) Reproducible print, 1964 April (Box 103)
      - Charles Van Dame Used as Restaurant. Sausilito, California (FBA-SFO-762) Reproducible print, 1962 July (Box 103)
      - Charles Van Dame, Abandoned Ferry, Juanita's Galley. Sausilito, California (FBA-SFO-762) Reproducible print, 1962 July (Box 103)
      - City of San Rafael, Abandoned Ferry Used as Home. Sausilito, California (FBA-SFO-762) Reproducible print, 1962 July (Box 103)
      - City of San Rafael, Abandoned Ferry Used as Home. Sausilito, California (FBA-SFO-762) Reproducible print, 1962 July (Box 103)
      - City of San Rafael, Abandoned Ferryboat Used as Home. Sausilito, California (FBA-SFO-762-4) Reproducible print, 1962 July (Box 103)
      - CNJ Ferry Boat Elizabeth Loads in the Liberty Street Stop (RR-NY - Marine operations) Study print, 1962 February (Box 103)
      - Cylinder Head, Belle of Louisville (1064-140) Reproducible (plus) print, 1964 October (Box 103)